people say it you have a lot of passion for what you doing
déconseille pillé les atermoiements cash-flow voiliers du rugby
and it's fully true the reason this
elle est fort un jeûne puis est
ah
pas
is because it's so hard
est écrase ce orange
if you don't
évidente
any rational person would give up
il y voit jean-paul ce débat
it's really hard
et sur le rire
and you have to do it over a sustained period time
elle est interdit aux postes spéculaient sans hein
so if you don't want it
ce fils rwandais
here i have a fondue and you don't really love it
chirac parfois dévoilé nürburgring en aval
by the year to give up
à et du débat
that's what happens to most people actually doing with it
la sofres grosses y sont une rue modeste
at at the ones that
l' attaque moines de
i cannot
à athènes
you be successful on hold the eyes of society in ones
il obéissait s' inscrit produira ce sera le mois de
often times it gets
trois femmes rester est
the ones that are successful launch what they did so they can persevere
de moins de musiques assure pourquoi plaidait serait épousent des
would you know we got we talk
oui le regard de retard
yeah and then once did
et un lien non moins net
didn't wanna
débandade
quiet
quoi
'cause are saying
ces usaid
like what put up with this that'd be a lot
mike ou moins paul incontestable tiroirs
so it's a lot of hard work
sarraute étant noire
can get it's a lot worrying constantly
et à l' et alexandra où les grâces des
yeah nah
et un à à prague
if you don't love it
et fils engrais
you fail
ufr
so you got a lot would not have passion
cela aurélien attache
and i think that's the higher worded the second thing is
elle a été gâtera humbert cinq vélizy
calm
un
you gotta be
il garde appuyée
you gotta be a really good talent scout
il cabillaud le reggae différentes air
is the matter how smart you are
c' est marasme royaume
you need a team of great people
un peu inutilisables cuivre
can you gotta figure out
et un libérales et gloire
haven't had a size people up really quickly make decisions without knowing people too well
à al sabah sans esprit pour apurer quoique oui mais pcg sonar de requis pour se voit en
can hire them and you see on t v one refine your intuition
et un ras-le-bol iosseliani dit on brûle soulagés
and be able to
un billet boxe
to help you know build an organization that can
c' est sûr qu' il en bureaux molles et chilienne
usually just
de choses
you build itself
ils ont louxor
jeannie great people and
j' y ai quoi